(Raj:)Stuart, is the Wil Wheaton signed up
for the Mystic Warlords Tournament...
(Raj:)...the Wil Wheaton from Star Trek?
(Stuart:)Yeah, he lives around here. Big gamer.
(Howard(phone rings):)Excuse me,
are you saying that Wil Wheaton...
...a.k.a. Ensign Wesley Crusher
on Star Trek: The Next Generation...
...is participating in your tournament?
(Stuart:)I'm sorry, did I rob you of the opportunity
to stumble onto that for yourself?
No, wait, you don't understand.
Growing up, I idolized Wil Wheaton.
You know, Wesley Crusher
had an eidetic memory just like me.
(Raj:)Oh, what a coincidence.
You can discuss that with him...
...while playing in the tournament.
Sign here.
Yeah, I was such a fan that in 1995
I traveled 10 hours by bus...
(Sheldon:)...to a sci-fi convention
in Jackson, Mississippi...
...wearing my Starfleet Academy
cadet uniform...
(Sheldon:)...in order to meet Wil Wheaton
and get him to autograph...
...my mint-in-package
Wesley Crusher action figure.
(Raj:)Oh, it'll be like a reunion then.
Sign here.
Yeah, my arduous journey, however,
was for naught.